<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Z Scores on Angeline Protacio</title>
    <link>https://www.angelineprotacio.com/tags/z-scores/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Z Scores on Angeline Protacio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.angelineprotacio.com/tags/z-scores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, Part 4</title>
      <link>https://www.angelineprotacio.com/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.angelineprotacio.com/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-4/</guid>
      <description>###Where were we? If you’re reading about my fantasy baseball experience for the first time, welcome! You may be better oriented by reading this first.  In the last three posts, I wrote about my draft strategy using projected WAR, and explored fantasy talent by defensive position. I discovered that WAR (Wins Above Replacement) was not a great way to select players given my league’s scoring categories. I calculated z-scores for my scoring categories instead, and looked at how that would have changed my draft picks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.angelineprotacio.com/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.angelineprotacio.com/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-3/</guid>
      <description>###Where were we? If you’re reading about my fantasy baseball experience for the first time, welcome! You may be better oriented by reading this first.  In the last two posts, I wrote about my draft strategy using projected WAR, and explored fantasy talent by defensive position. I discovered that WAR (Wins Above Replacement) was not a great way to select players given my league’s scoring categories. In the absence of a summary statistic to guide my decisions, I looked at all of the scoring categories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>