<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Angeline Protacio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Angeline Protacio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, Part 1</title>
      <link>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-1/</guid>
      <description>My first season in Fantasy Baseball What is Fantasy Baseball? The Draft How I Prepared for the Draft My Draft Strategy Up Next   My first season in Fantasy Baseball I joined an ESPN Fantasy Baseball League for the first time this year, which may come as a shock to those of you who know that I love both baseball and data. I was in an ESPN Fantasy Basketball League a few years ago, but because I haven’t watched basketball seriously in about 15 years, these were two very unsatisfying seasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, Part 2</title>
      <link>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-2/</guid>
      <description>So where are we now? Other Considerations: Positions for Feast or Famine But were they, though? Up Next   

So where are we now? If you’re reading about my fantasy baseball experience for the first time, welcome! You may be better oriented by reading this first.  In the previous post, I wrote about my draft strategy using WAR, and how I selected Posey, a catcher, in the second round, and Simmons, a shortstop, in the fourth round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, part 3</title>
      <link>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Okay, now where were we? There is another way! Up Next   Okay, now where were we? If you’re reading about my fantasy baseball experience for the first time, welcome! You may be better oriented by reading this first.  In the last two posts, I wrote about my draft strategy using projected WAR, and explored fantasy talent by defensive position. I discovered that WAR (Wins Above Replacement) was not a great way to select players given my league’s scoring categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Batters in Fantasy Baseball, Part 4</title>
      <link>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/drafting-batters-part-4/</guid>
      <description>End of Season Results What-if land Lessons Learned Next Steps   End of Season Results Team Expectations vs. Reality Up until this point, we’ve been looking at stat projections for 2018, but now that the season is over, we can see just how these projections played out. Let’s bring in the final 2018 stats from Fangraphs, and compare them to the projected stats. I’ve renamed all final stats to include the f_ prefix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>