<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Angeline Protacio</title>
    <link>/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Angeline Protacio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Album Discoverer</title>
      <link>/portfolio/album-discoverer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/album-discoverer/</guid>
      <description>Who Still Listens to Albums? Getting the Data Principal Components Analysis Artist and Genre - It’s Messy Validating My PCA Artist and Album Examples Recommending Albums Introducing the Album Discoverer Flask App Areas for Improvement   Who Still Listens to Albums? Before the days of streaming music and listening to MP3s, I spent a decent chunk of money on buying CDs. The act of popping a newly acquired CD into a player and listening to an album in its entirety is a lot less familiar now, partly because no one buys CDs anymore, but also because listening to music has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webscraping Baseball Data using Python</title>
      <link>/portfolio/webscraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/webscraping/</guid>
      <description>Why Scrape Baseball Data? Scraping Fangraphs Scraping Baseball Reference Wrap Up   Why Scrape Baseball Data? In my desire to improve my fantasy team, I realized I was lacking data on quality starts, and thought it would be good to predict this. Before I could start modeling, I needed historical season data and projections, to form the basis for my training, validation, and test data. I planned to get this all from Baseball Reference and Fangraphs, neither of which has an API that makes it easy to get their data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>